FELIX WANG

Phone: (816) 273-4498

Email: felixtwang1337@gmail.com

Address: 3104 N 34th Ter, Saint Joseph, Missouri 64506-4328

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Skilled communicator, writer and reader who can connect with other people easily. Able to work together in groups to accomplish large goals through innovative problem solving and expert use of technology. Wide range of knowledge in multiple areas such as history, arts, science, and computers.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020 Columbia, Missouri

Tournament Director, RAFT II

• Compile information on various academic topics to write several high quality quizbowl questions for use at national tournaments. Directed a tournament with eighteen teams that ran for 6 hours on November 07, 2020.

Dec. 2019 – Oct. 2020 Columbia, Missouri

Writer, IO Saturnalia

• Conduct research to obtain information and authentic detail, using sources such as newspaper accounts, diaries, and books. That research was used in order to write and submit thirteen high quality guizbowl guestions which were used at several national high school events

May. 2019 - Sep. 2019 Saint Joseph, Missouri

Busser, Cheddars

- Clean or sanitize work areas, utensils, or equipment.
- Perform cleaning duties such as sweeping, mopping, and washing dishes, to keep equipment and facilities sanitary.

Apr. 2019 - Sep. 2019 Columbia, Missouri

Writer, RAFT

• Refer to reference materials, such as textbooks, encyclopedias, and documentaries, in order to write and submit forty-five high quality quizbowl questions utilized across the country.

EDUCATION

Present

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

• University of Missouri - Columbia, Missouri

LANGUAGES

Chinese Fluent French Proficient

SKILLS

Creativity Skillful

Reading Comprehension Expert

Critical Thinking Experienced Computers Skillful

Writing Experienced

AWARDS

Summa Cum Laude- Central High School-2018 National Honor Society- Central High School-2018 Mayor's Special Distinction Award-2017 Honor's College- University of Missouri-Present 1 Rating- MSHSAA State Music Contest-2018 Outstanding School District Recognition- 2018 AP Scholar

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Central Quizbowl National Qualifier- 4 years player, 1-year Captain Central Swim Team Captain- 4 years swimmer, 1-year Captain